[{"answer": "Respect, affection, traveling together.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 46, "question": "How do you manage to do this and why can't more of your colleagues do this?", "qSentId": 45}, {"answer": "Well, in fairness to our colleagues, Piers, there are a lot of real close friendships around this place.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "Senator Graham, what is the secret to proper bipartisanship, do you think?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "IEBERMAN: Oh, yes.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 143, "question": "Have you ever known him not lose his temper?", "qSentId": 142}, {"answer": "Actually, I'm comfortable.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "Or are you comfortable with where things are?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "Well, there are limits.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "Why aren't there limits on the number of guns and the type of guns?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "You're going to blame the British?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "Because I enjoy shooting.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "Why do you want eight guns?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "Yes, it is.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 268, "question": "That argument has gone, hasn't it?", "qSentId": 267}, {"answer": "You know what, the question is whether we have the political will to put the deal together that most people on both sides, both parties will tell you is what has to happen and that is, yes, raise taxes, raise revenues.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 282, "question": "Where is this deal, in the end, do you think, going to wash up?", "qSentId": 281}, {"answer": "Well, yes.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 292, "question": "You've got to be very careful where you encourage the cutting of entitlements, right?", "qSentId": 291}, {"answer": "Don't go out -- don't go out and continue the campaign that is over.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 321, "question": "ORGAN: But why isn't that happening?", "qSentId": 320}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "But can you tell me what you saw?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "I didn't see anybody with their hands up.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "Did you see people being escorted out of the mall with their hands in the air?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "I did see the Santa stuff.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "Were you close enough to witness any of that?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "It was horrifying.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "What was that scene like?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "David, there was also another witness that said that people were locked inside the mall, that they were told to stay where they were, but you were able to get out?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "Any information about the actual investigation is not going to be appropriate to release right now.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "Do you think it's random?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "I don't -- I was not here.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "Did they do everything they were supposed to in situations like this?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "I don't have any identifying information.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "Can you us more about the two victims?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "I don't have any information about the investigation at this is point that I can share.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 462, "question": "Can you confirm that?", "qSentId": 461}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "Any minor injure?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "I do not have that information.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "Were you folks in contact with mall security watching it unfold on video camera?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "There's still police officers inside the mall.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 474, "question": "How many people are still in there?", "qSentId": 473}, {"answer": "I doubt that it will be released at 8:00.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "And do you expect his name to be released at 8:00?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "It was an adult male.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "What can you tell us about him?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "That's the extent of the information I've been given.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "Was he 20S, 30s, 40s?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "I don't have that information for you.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "Was he wearing a mask?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "I'm --", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "Were any shots fired outside the mall?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "I don't have any information about the shooter to share with anybody.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "Did the shooter shoot anybody outside the mall?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "I do not know.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "Has law enforcement identified the shooter?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "I think part of it's generational.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "Do you think that younger people don't care nearly as much about it as their parents and grandparents?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "RAHAM: Well, here's what --", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 552, "question": "But can they both be equal?", "qSentId": 551}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 559, "question": "Can I answer this?", "qSentId": 558}, {"answer": "I -- I think that marriage ought to be decided by the states.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "What do you think they should decide?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "Of course it is.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 586, "question": "Well, is it possible for three people to genuinely love each other and want to share their lives together?", "qSentId": 585}, {"answer": "Uh, I would say not.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 588, "question": "OK, then, is it OK to have three people marry each other?", "qSentId": 587}, {"answer": "Because the point is simply a homosexual couple's right to get married in the same way as the heterosexual couple in America.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 597}, {"answer": "You know what we're dealing with --", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 631, "question": "Would you allow slavery in some states but not others?", "qSentId": 630}, {"answer": "What the experts tell me, at least the ones I've talked to, it's really a gateway drug that may lead to more drug addiction.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 657, "question": "And very quickly on pot, are you in favor of legalizing pot?", "qSentId": 656}, {"answer": "RAHAM: No.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 661, "question": "-- have you ever inhaled?", "qSentId": 660}, {"answer": "-- I don't -- I don't pretend to be normal.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 667, "question": "-- just to find out?", "qSentId": 666}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 670, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 669}, {"answer": "At the end of the day, I -- I -- I want to be me.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 675, "question": "How abnormal are you?", "qSentId": 674}, {"answer": "Obviously, I think all of us, and all Americans, a resolution of this issue of the fiscal cliff so that people can live next year with a sense of predictability, with a sense that they are going to have a growing economy, and, frankly, peace in the world.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 697, "question": "What would you most like, politically, as a gift?", "qSentId": 696}, {"answer": "Oh, I -- I think it would be fun to do.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 699, "question": "And a place on this committee?", "qSentId": 698}, {"answer": "Christmas and Hanukah.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 703, "question": "Senator Lieberman?", "qSentId": 702}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 710, "question": "So, uh, what -- what would I really like from the president?", "qSentId": 709}, {"answer": "Three things.", "docId": "121211pmt", "aSentId": 716, "question": "Senator Graham?", "qSentId": 715}]